const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"She said that her mother's name ____. Lena.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"is",3:"has been",4:"were"}},{type:"test",question:"I saw what he ____",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was doing",2:"is doing",3:"are doing",4:"has doing"}},{type:"test",question:"She thought her new acquaintance ____ smart.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"is",3:"were",4:"has been"}},{type:"test",question:"Jane told me that Kazakhstan ____ than Germany.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was bigger",2:"is being bigger",3:"has been bigger",4:"is bigger"}},{type:"test",question:"I told everyone that I ____ to the party at ten, but ____ as soon as possible.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"couldn't come, would arrive",2:"can't come, would arrive",3:"couldn't come, arrive",4:"can't come, will arrive"}},{type:"test",question:'"How are your parents?" she asked. I answered that they ____ very well.',rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were",2:"have been",3:"are",4:"were being"}},{type:"test",question:"He said that his car ____ a few days ago.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"had been stolen",2:"was stolen",3:"has been stolen",4:"is stolen"}},{type:"test",question:"He said he ____ hungry.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"was",2:"will be",3:"is",4:"has been"}},{type:"test",question:"I heard she ____ good English.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"spoke",2:"speaks",3:"speak",4:"is speaking"}},{type:"test",question:"I had to confess to my boyfriend that I ____ like football.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"didn't",2:"doesn't",3:"will not",4:"do not"}},{type:"test",question:"It was announced that the international treaty against the new warfare ____ and had gone into effect.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"had been ratified",2:"would have been ratified",3:"is ratified",4:"was ratified"}},{type:"test",question:"The receptionist tells us that from our room we ____ a wonderful view over the sea.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"will have",2:"would have",3:"were going to have",4:"were having"}},{type:"test",question:"Kate replied that she ____ surprised at not seeing him at the lesson.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would not be",2:"is not",3:"has not been",4:"won't be"}},{type:"test",question:"The guide reminded us that after lunch we ____ sightseeing.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"were going",2:"go",3:"went",4:"would go"}},{type:"test",question:"Liza assured me that the party ____ a great fun. But in fact, it wasn't.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"would be",2:"will be",3:"have been",4:"will have been"}}]}]};export{e as default};
